我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends
我秘密地打击犯罪
at S.T.A.R. Labs, I fight crime
寻找跟我一样的超能力者
and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so, I opened up our world to new threats,
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我叫闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on he Flash...
我们宇宙中真有一个洞
There is, indeed, a hole in our universe
通往他的地球
which leads to his Earth.
见见地球二来的哈里森·威尔斯博士
Meet Dr. Harrison Wells from Earth-2.
你觉得我们到亲晚安吻的阶段了吗
Do you think we've reached the good-night kiss stage?
极速对速度非常痴迷
Zoom is obsessed with speed.
极速一直在把超能力者
He has been sending meta-humans from your world
从你的世界送到这边来与我战斗
through the breaches to fight me.
她的名字叫做光博士
Her name is Doctor Light.
你好啊  美女
Hello, gorgeous.
你想从我这得到什么
What do you want from me?
你的命
Your life.
我看到了我自己
I saw myself.
看来你有个邪恶的超能力双胞胎
Sounds like you have an evil meta-twin.
你在哪
Where are you?
我就在这
I'm right here.
我是来杀你的  闪电侠  准备燃烧吧
I'm here to kill you, Flash, so get ready to fry.
来吧
Bring it on.
我就说吧
Told you.
极速永远是赢家
Zoom always wins.
72小时前
极速派我来杀你
Zoom sent me here to kill you,
但我不想
but I didn't want to.
杀琳达·帕克你倒没意见
But you were fine with killing Linda Park.
这是我能想到的最好的坏主意了
It was the best bad idea I could come up with.
让极速发现她的尸体
Leave her body for Zoom to find,
他就会以为我死了  我就自由了
he'd think I was dead, and I'd be free.
他怎么知道在哪能找到她的尸体
How was he supposed to know where to find her body?
放我走吧
Just let me go.
让我消失
Let me disappear.
你的余生都将担惊受怕
You would spend the rest of your life looking over your shoulder,
不知极速何时会找上你
never knowing when Zoom is coming.
那好  敢问您有何妙计
Okay. And what's your great idea?
要是你杀了我  你该怎么联系极速
How were you supposed to contact him after you killed me?
我该拿走某个东西...
I was supposed to get something--
只有你死了我才能拿到的东西...
something I could only get if you were dead--
然后从传送门扔过去作为证据
and then throw it through the breach as proof.
-然后呢  -然后他就会来找我
- And then what? - Then he'd come for me.
确认我杀了你  然后带我回家
Confirm the kill and bring me home.
-你为什么要问这些  -因为我想找到他
- Why do you want to know? - Because I want to find him.
你不会想找到他的
You really don't.
他会不断派人杀我
He's gonna keep coming for me.
他会不断绑架像你一样的人
He's gonna keep kidnapping people like you,
强迫他们为他效力
forcing them to do what he wants.
我要阻止他害死更多人
I have to stop him before more people die.
-你阻止不了极速的  -我能行
- You can't stop Zoom. - Yes, I can.
我会的  但我需要你的帮助
I will, but I need your help.
极速想让光博士把你的新徽章拿给他
Zoom wants Doctor Light to send him your new emblem.
对  我们就用它作诱饵
Yes. We need it for bait.
如果我们让光博士拿走我的徽章
If we can get Doctor Light to take my emblem,
从缺口扔过去
throw it through the breach,
极速就会来找我的尸体  我们就能抓住他
then Zoom will come to collect my body, and we can trap him.
你知道那徽章做起来要费好大功夫吧
You know it took a lot of work to make that emblem, right?
这个女人为了逃脱极速的掌控
This is the woman who was willing to kill Linda
连琳达都愿意杀
in order to escape Zoom,
现在她却肯帮我们抓他吗
but now she's willing to help us catch him?
她知道别无他法
She knows it's the only way.
在我离开地球二之前
Before I left Earth-2,
我在研究一种能让极速变迟缓的血清
I worked on a serum to dampen Zoom's speed.
只需要拉蒙设计一种能发射血清的武器
All we would need is for Ramon to develop a weapon to deliver it.
太好了  这可能会成为今年新版的冷冻枪
Oh, great, that could be this year's cold gun.
或许会落入另一个罪犯之手
Maybe another criminal can get it,
然后就会出现个"迟缓警官"
and then we'd have Sergeant Slow.
我绝不会让这种事发生
I would never let that happen.
"迟缓警官"这个名字逊爆了
Sergeant Slow is a terrible name.
我们是不是忘记了极速看起来
Are we forgetting how much more powerful
比巴里强大多少吗
than Barry Zoom seems to be?
假如巴里都能抓住子弹
I mean, if Barry can catch bullets,
还有什么是射向极速时他抓不到的
what's to say Zoom can't catch whatever you shoot at him?
出其不意  给他来点小惊喜
Surprise-- the element of surprise.
我们可以设定发射装置在
All we would do is rig a projectile to fire
极速穿过裂隙时发射
as Zoom crosses into the breach.
他无法阻止意料不到的东西
He can't stop what he can't see coming.
-这主意不错  -谢谢
- That's great. - Thanks.
乔  你来说句公道话
Joe, voice of reason here?
我们需要制定个计划  刚才那个就不错
We need a plan. That's as good as any.
只要他能做出来就行
As long as he can deliver.
别小瞧我  警探
Don't underestimate me, Detective.
帕蒂需要咱们回警局一趟
Oh, Patty needs us back at the station.
到地方见  好吧
I'll meet you there, all right?
你是不是忘了杰伊的话
Are you just forgetting everything Jay told us
现在开始支持威尔斯了
and supporting Wells now?
没有  我压根就不相信威尔斯
Oh, no, I don't trust Wells at all.
我只是想摸清他的意图
I just want to see what he's up to.
我想给他抛出点诱饵  让他自己上钩
I figure we give him some rope, he'll hang himself.
完全赞同  我觉得他有所隐瞒
Yeah, I'm totally with you. I think he's hiding something.
以我这么多年审讯犯人的经验来看
Look, my hunch after interrogating suspects all these years,
这家伙肯定不对劲
something's not right with this dude.
巴里跟我说了你的能耐
Barry told me about this thing you can do?
-震波  -天啊  别激动
- Vibing. - Oh, God, just relax.
可以用在威尔斯身上吗
Can you do it with Wells?
可以一试
I can try.
办不到
Incapable?
这么告诉你吧
Well, let me tell you something.
假如你不能校准量子螺旋
If you are incapable of aligning the quantum helix
还有顺便说一下
and, by the way,
这是你在尖端科研实验室的本职工作
the sole purpose of your employment here at S.T.A.R. Labs,
那就请你帮我节省点时间精力
could you save me some time and effort?
请你去给我找一个
Could you go out there and find someone
能代替你完成工作的人来
who can actually do your job for you?
又来了
There it is.
工作腔
Work voice.
我小时候你带我来尖端科研实验室
When I was little and you used to bring me to S.T.A.R. Labs with you.
当时我被吓坏了
It used to freak me out
你在这里和在家说话的样子完全不同
how differently you talked here than when you were at home.
跟你妈妈一样  你这会儿不应该在学校吗
You and your mother both. Shouldn't you be at school?
我十五岁就高中毕业了  老爸
I graduated high school when I was 15, Dad.
-好吧  -大学逃课一天没事儿的
- Right. - Can miss a day of college.
这才是我家杰西  思维总是那么敏捷
Ah, that's my Jess, always so quick.
-所以呢  -所以什么
- So? - So?
是真的吗
Is it true?
你说什么
Is what true?
闪电侠在新闻发布会上有关你的言论
What The Flash said about you at the press conference?
说你的粒子加速器创造出了超能力者
That your particle accelerator created the meta-humans?
这个  杰西
It is-- Jesse--
你为什么没告诉我
Why didn't you just tell me?
看来  杰伊·加里克
Jay Garrick, it turns out,
归咎责任的速度
is much faster at assigning blame
比他救人时还要更快
than he is at actual heroics.
爸爸  闪电侠是英雄
Dad, The Flash is a hero.
我一直都不理解你为什么如此不待见他
Okay, I've never understood why you disliked him so much,
现在我明白了  因为他知道你做了什么
but now I know it's because he knew what you'd done.
我在尖端科研实验室所做的
What I've done at S.T.A.R. Labs
是改变世界的  杰西
is change the world, Jesse,
解开宇宙的秘密
unlocking the mysteries of the universe.
有时候如果你没有解锁需要的钥匙
And when you don't have the key to the lock,
就不得不把门踢开
sometimes you have to kick in the door.
你应该回学校去了
You should get to school.
不用操心  今天我已经被上一课了
Don't worry. I got my education today.
你是我的快乐之源啊  杰西·快客
You're my joy, Jesse Quick.
中城警局
-好的  再见  -再见  乔
- All right. Talk to you later. - See you, Joe.
你可算来了
Great, you're here.
你也早安  帕蒂
Good morning to you too, Patty.
我昨晚弄光博士的案子一宿没睡
Yes, I was up all night working on the Doctor Light case.
我一直在试图预想
I-I've been trying to anticipate
在她能控制光能的前提下
all the powers she might throw our way,
可以向我们发射多大的能量
you know, on the premise that she can manipulate light energy.
-辛苦了  但  -你知道
- I appreciate it, but-- - Did you know
光能可以转化为强光吗
that light energy can be turned into hard light?
这可能听起来很荒唐  但这是事实
I mean, that doesn't even sound like a thing, but it is.
好了  帕蒂
Seriously, Patty--
还有  光的另一个用途就是隐形
No, and on the other end of the spectrum is invisibility.
这虽然就是个设想  我觉得
Look, it--it's just hypothetical, but I think that--
光博士这个案子已经结了
The Doctor Light case is closed.
好吧
Oh, uh, okay.
你能告诉我为什么吗
Can you tell me why?
不能
No.
No?
-好吧  -你好啊
- Okay. - Hey.
-早上好  -你还好吗
- Hi! - Are you good?
我挺好的
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
不过你老爸刚才狠狠地回绝了我
Your dad just shut me down in a big way.
-什么意思  -我也说不清  就是
- What do you mean? - I-I don't know. It just--
你说这会不会是因为
You don't think
我们俩之前接吻了
it's because you and I kissed?
我觉得他不知道这事  我什么都没说
No, I don't think he knows. I didn't say anything,
你想的话  我倒是可以找他谈谈
but I can talk to him if you want.
不用了  我会跟他谈谈的
No, no, no, I'll talk to him.
他是我的搭档
You know, he's my partner.
我们之间不存在任何信任和沟通问题
We should have trust and communication.
你确定吗  我不介意跟他说我们接吻的事啊
Are you sure? I don't mind talking about that kiss.
那个吻非常美妙
It was a good kiss.
是的  不过关于那个吻
Yeah, yeah, although the memory--
我已经记的不太清楚了
it's a little foggy.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
我可能需要你提醒我一下
I might need, like, a reminder soon.
好啊
Okay.
中城新闻图报
闪电侠有跟你讨论过
Have you had any word from The Flash
那个杀害拉尔金的超能力者吗
about the meta-human that killed Larkin?
还没有  但是他应该已经在调查了
No, not yet, but I know he's working on it.
也许我能跟他谈谈
You know, maybe I could talk to him.
琳达  我觉得还是算了吧
Linda, I don't think that's a good idea.
拉尔金死了
Look, Larkin is dead,
我现在根本无法集中注意力
which makes it really hard for me to concentrate
做实体报道  去揭露丑闻
on field goals and doping scandals.
我不想坐在这里  听大家跟我说
I don't want to sit around being told not to worry
没什么好担心的
my pretty little head about it.
我理解  真的
I get that. Believe me, I do.
那就告诉他我想尽一份力
Then tell him I want to help.
我不能让跟我长着同一张脸的女人再害人了
Please, I can't let this woman who looks like me hurt anyone else.
我会再问问他的
I'll ask again.
不过相信我  闪电侠已经把局面控制好了
But trust me, Flash has everything under control.
糟了
Crap.
光博士隐形了
Doctor Light's gone invisible.
把门锁好
Lock the doors.
把门都关上
Shut the doors!
门不听指令
The doors aren't responding.
安全程序都没有反应
None of the security protocols are responding.
她黑进了安全系统
She's hacked the system.
巴里  光博士逃了
Barry, Doctor Light is escaping.
她在哪里
Where is she?
光博士想办法黑进了牢房里的灯光
Doctor Light managed to hack into the lights of her cell.
整栋楼的照明系统使用了光导纤维
The whole building runs on fiber optics
会不断发出光脉冲
that operate on pulses of light,
所以她把阻尼器关掉后使用了能力
so she turned off the dampeners and used her powers.
我跟你说过她很危险
I told you how dangerous she was.
你之前就该听我的给她打一针镇静剂
You should have listened to me and sedated her.
我以为我已经说服她
I thought I had convinced her that helping us
只有帮我们才能免受极速的骚扰
was the only way she'd free herself from Zoom.
-只能说你想错了  -是啊
- Well, you thought wrong. - Yeah.
听着
Okay, look,
光博士已经逃了  就别互相责备了
Doctor Light is gone, so instead of assigning blame,
先想想接下里要怎么做吧
let's try to figure out what we're gonna do next.
你觉得她会再去杀琳达吗
Do you think she's gonna try and take Linda again?
我让爱瑞丝把琳达带回家了
I had Iris bring Linda to the house,
看着她点  以防万一
just in case, to keep an eye on her.
速度抑制器弄得怎么样了
How are we doing with the speed-dampener?
我们已经分离了合成物
I think we isolated the composite.
我们正在改造绿箭用来抓威尔斯的镖
And we're modifying the dart The Arrow used to take down Wells.
他不是威尔斯  我才是
He's not Wells. I'm Wells.
随便你怎么说了  哈里
Whatever, Harry.
可是我们都不知道这能不能行
But we don't even really know if this thing works.
不试验不会知道  这次就是实体测试
Until we try it, no. This will be a field test,
所以大家能不要啰嗦  回去干正事了吗
so can we end this scintillating staff meeting and get back to work?
我觉得我要说一下大家真正的想法
Or how about I say what everybody's thinking?
也许光博士逃走也是一件好事
Maybe it's a good thing that Doctor Light is gone.
也许这是宇宙在阻止我们
Maybe it's the universe stopping us
犯下更愚蠢的错误
from doing something really stupid.
不  不  不能停
No. No. Keep going.
我会找出其他办法对付极速的
I'm gonna figure out another way to get Zoom.
你慢点  我想和你谈谈
Hey, slow your roll. I want to talk to you.
乔  我知道我在做什么
Joe, look, I know what I'm doing.
我不知道  所以为什么不提点我一下
Okay, I don't, so why don't you clue me in?
我在试图阻止极速
I'm trying to stop Zoom.
我还以为你也同意呢
I thought you were on board with that.
在保持开放的心态
I'm keeping my options open.
我不知道你为什么认为我们还有得选
I don't understand why you think we have a choice.
极速想让我死
Zoom wants me dead.
他从地球二送来的那些超能力者
The meta-humans that he's sending from Earth-2,
他们可不关心挡在前边的无辜群众
they don't care how many innocent people get in the way.
看看爱瑞丝和琳达上司的下场吧
Look at what happened to Iris and Linda's boss.
他就是与极速战争中的附带伤害
He was just collateral damage in Zoom's war.
下一次  就可能是你或是爱瑞丝
The next time, that could be you or Iris.
我只是觉得现在去面对他太早了
I'm just wondering if going after him now is premature.
我是说  我们都不知道他有什么能力
I mean, we barely know anything about his abilities.
威尔斯知道
Wells does.
你还真信任那个
You're putting a whole lot of faith
和杀死你母亲的凶手长得一模一样的人
in the man wearing the face of your mother's killer.
我觉得我们应该去找杰伊  让他帮咱们
I think we should find Jay, get him to help us on this.
杰伊说得很清楚  他不想帮助我被杀
Yeah, Jay made it pretty clear that he doesn't want to help get me killed,
而我们也不能就这么袖手旁观
and we can't just sit around
等着极速进行下一步计划
and wait for Zoom to make his next move anymore.
我们不能
We can't.
不是你跟我说生活中不能总是被动防守
Aren't you the one who told me life isn't about playing defense,
有时候想要成功就要主动出击吗
sometimes the only way to succeed is by working the offense?
我记得那个时候我们说的是
I think at the time we were talking about
你高中橄榄球队的选拔赛
your high school football tryouts.
你说过不再提这事了
You said you'd never bring that up again.
我只是想说  用那个...
I just wanted to say using the,
钨基复合材料来抑制振动  这办法真是
tungsten composite to dampen vibrations, that was--
真是挺绝的
that was pretty brilliant.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在祝贺你
I'm congratulating you.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
我这可是在恭敬你呢
Wow, try to give a guy a compliment.
你不是想要恭敬我
You're not trying to give me a compliment.
你是在插手你不该管的事情
You're trying to meddle into things that are none of your business.
-你为什么要对我用震波  -没有啊
- What did you vibe about me? - Nothing.
天呐  我为什么要对你用震波
God, why? What's there to vibe on?
别碰我  如果你有问题  就问
Don't touch me. If you have questions, ask them.
不然的话就离我远点
Otherwise stay away from me.
怎样
So?
天呐  还以为杀人恶魔的版本
God, you'd think the serial killer version
会是比较混蛋的那个
would've been the bigger jerk.
你碰他的时候发生了什么吗
What happened when you touched him?
你看到了什么
What did you see?
我什么都没看到
Oh, I didn't see anything.
再去碰他一次
Go touch him again.
不行了  他现在警惕我了
No, he's onto me now.
你得继续尝试
Well, you have to keep trying.
我觉得乔是对的
I mean, I think Joe's right.
威尔斯和极速之间绝对发生了什么
Something must have happened between Wells and Zoom,
让这事变成私人恩怨
made this personal.
星城的绿箭 之前曾是兜帽男
The Arrow of Starling City, formerly known as The Hood,
被发现真身原来是亿万富翁罗伯特·奎恩
has been unmasked as billionaire Robert Queen.
当他的船只在太平洋沉没后
Robert was marooned on an island
罗伯特被困在一座孤岛上
when his boat went down in the Pacific,
一起事故导致了他的儿子  奥利弗之死
an accident that ended with the tragic death of his son, Oliver.
罗伯特·奎恩当时被认为死亡...
Robert Queen was thought dead when--
兜帽男真面目
请稍等  我们刚收到信息
Excuse me, I'm receiving word.
超能力者袭击中城大学
中城大学刚发生了一起袭击事件
There has been an attack at Central City College.
科研大楼是另一起超能力袭击的目标
The science building was the focus of another meta-human attack.
我们刚收到一段视频
We are just receiving video.
请注意  我被告知
Please be advised, I'm being told
您接下来将看到的视频...
that the footage you're about to see...
杰西  是爸爸  你能不能...
Hey, Jesse, it's Dad. Can you--
我刚看到新闻
I just-I saw on the news--
给我回电好吗  给我报个平安
Just call me, all right? Let me know that you're okay.
让我知道你没...
That you weren't--
超能力者袭击中城大学
目击者称闪电侠抵达了现场
Witnesses report that The Flash arrived on the scene
但在那之前  超能力者罪犯已经
but not before the hostile meta-human
挟持了一名女学生逃走了
escaped with a hostage-- a female student.
我们还不知道她的身份
We have not yet ID'd her,
而且也不知道为什么她会成为袭击者的目标
and there is no indication as to why she has been specifically targeted.
不
No.
中城警局
乔  警探  我们能谈谈吗
Joe-- detective-- can we talk for a minute?
如果是关于光博士的事
If this is about Doctor Light--
不  是  不
No, yeah-- no.
可能吧  不过听我说
Maybe, but okay, look.
我想我明白了最近这几天
I think I figured out why you've been
你为什么不太爱说话了
a bit shut down the last couple of days.
是吗
Really?
是的  我感觉你并没有把一切都告诉我
Yeah, I feel like you're not being completely transparent with me,
不过我觉得这是我的错
but I think that it's my fault.
你是个很好的  优秀  出色的警探
Look, you're a great-- excellent-- wonderful detective,
所以我觉得你能感觉到
and I think you can sense
我并没有把一切都告诉你
I'm not being completely transparent with you.
你感觉的没错  我们是搭档
And you're right. Look, we're partners.
我们应该坦诚相待
We need to be completely honest with each other.
-不能有秘密  -帕蒂
- No secrets... - Patty.
巴里和我接吻了
Barry and I kissed.
你也太坦诚了
There's something to being too transparent.
不不不  我觉得
No, no, no, no, I think that it's great
把一切都出来是最好的
that everything's just out there, right out in the open.
你跟巴里私下里做什么
Whatever you and Barry do in private
那是你的事
is your own business.
好吧
Okay.
这么说你没生我的气
So you're not mad at me?
我发誓  我一点都不关心
I promise you, I could care less.
太好了  我感觉好多了
Great, I feel so much better.
有没有什么事
Is there anything, you know,
你想要告诉我的呢
maybe you've been meaning to tell me?
我们是搭档
We're partners--
跟彼此要坦诚相待
totally transparent with each other.
没有
Nope.
好吧
Cool.
你们是要开派对吗
Are you guys having a dinner party?
我看也是
You would think.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
有时做饭能让我放松下来
It's just, sometimes cooking helps me to relax.
你有光博士的消息吗
Have you heard anything about Doctor Light?
我还有危险吗
Am I still in danger?
-我们还不确定  -拜托
- We're not really sure. - Come on.
-我快要疯了  巴里  -这是真的
- I'm going crazy here, Barry. - Yeah, she is.
蛋糕来了
That is the cake.
希望你们都饿了
Hope you're hungry.
她不是开玩笑
She's not kidding.
这些吃的都可以养活一直军队了
There's enough food in there to feed an army.
她一定是吓坏了
She must be terrified.
应该说是愤怒
More like furious.
拉尔金为了保护她而死了
Larkin died trying to protect her,
而且更不幸的是
and it only makes it worse
凶手竟然跟她长得一模一样  相信我
that the person who did it looks just like her. I mean, trust me.
如果琳达现在有光博士的能力
If Linda had Doctor Light's powers right now...
怎么了
What?
琳达和光博士 她们长得一模一样
I just, Linda and Light-- they're identical.
以至于光博士觉得可以用琳达骗过极速
So identical that Light even thought she could fool Zoom.
现在我们有光博士的衣服
Now we have Light's suit.
你什么都不用说了  我知道
You don't even have to say anything, I know.
-这个想法太糟了  -不不不  挺好
- It's a terrible idea. - No, no, no, it's not.
我们可以让极速认为琳达就是光博士
We make Zoom think that Linda is Doctor Light
然后利用她把他引出来
and use her to draw him out.
这太危险了  对吧
It's too dangerous, right?
让琳达来决定吧
Let Linda decide.
她非常想要抓住
I mean, she's desperate to catch the person
杀死拉金的凶手
who's responsible for Larkin's death,
而且她应该得到这个帮我们的机会
and she deserves the chance to help us.
好吧
Okay.
我还是不明白我为什么要来这里
I still don't understand why we're here.
你老爸不是说不要离开家吗
I thought your dad said not to leave the house.
-有人想跟你谈谈  -谁
- Someone wants to talk to you. - Who?
帕克女士  我需要你的帮助
Ms. Park, I need your help.
伙计
Dude.
你干这个多久了
How long you been sitting on this?
有兴趣爱好很重要
It's important to have hobbies.
这太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
不  并不荒唐
No, it's not.
你跟光博士长得一模一样
You look just like Doctor Light.
再戴上这副西斯科研制的手套
And with these gloves that Cisco rigged up,
你就可以拥有和她一样的能力
you'll be able to do what she does.
别担心  绝对安全的
Don't worry, they are totally safe.
-差不多吧  -差不多
- Ish. - Ish?
拜托  这是真的
Well, come on, it's gotta be believable,
它们的确可以发射火焰并使物体爆炸
so they really do fire and explode things.
在她熟悉手套的用法之前
And you are going to have to let her
你要让她练习一下怎么发射能量波
hit you with those blasts when she gets the hang of it.
到底是谁想出这么烂的主意的
Who exactly came up with this terrible idea?
行了  这不是烂主意
Okay, it's not a terrible idea.
他的战衣可以吸收能量波
The suit can absorb the blasts.
真的还是差不多
For real or ish?
你觉得什么才算是个烂主意呢  西斯科
What does a terrible idea look like to you, Cisco?
好吧  你知道吗  我更愿意相信
Okay, you know what? I like to think
自己能够看到事情好的一面  行吗
I can see the bright side of things, okay?
积极一点  各位
Positivity, people.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
攻击那些模型里面我的那个  知道吗
So just hit the ones of me. Okay?
-明白  -很好
- Got it. - Great.
光博士
Doctor Light.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我还是稍微调整一下  给我螺丝刀
I'm just gonna adjust those a little. Screwdriver.
来了  来了
Coming. Coming.
就...
Just--
好了  和刚才的相反
Okay, so, do the opposite of that,
就差不多了
and we'll have it.
着火了
It's on fire.
对不起
Ooh, sorry.
我的错
My bad.
我做到了  你们看见了吗
I did it! Did you see that?
是啊
Yeah!
你们没事吗  还好吗
You all good? You okay?
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧  无意冒犯琳达  但绝不能
Okay, no offense to Linda, but there is no way
让她来做这件事
she can pull this off.
或许她不再每次放火都尖叫还可以试试
Well, maybe if she didn't scream every time she fired.
琳达刚开始不太适应  但她能胜任
Yup, Linda had a rocky start, but she can pull this off.
我知道她可以的
I know she can.
好吧  你有没有找到靠近缺口
All right, did you find someplace near breach where
同时又没有市民的地方呢
we don't have to worry about civilians getting in the way?
是的  码头边上有个地方
Yeah, there's a place by the docks
那里通常晚上都没有人
that's usually deserted at night.
好极了  速度阻尼器怎么样了
Awesome. How are we doing with the speed-dampener?
我的测试显示它会起效的
My tests indicate that it should work.
会起效的
It will work.
我会调整拉蒙做的手套  确保其功效更佳
I'll tune up Ramon's gloves, makes sure they work better.
好  很好
Okay, great.
我们真的要这样做吗
Hey, we're actually gonna go through with this?
是的  我们要做
Yeah, we're doing this.
我让爱瑞丝为琳达做好准备
I'm gonna have Iris get Linda ready.
好的  我去跟他说
Yeah, I'll go talk to him.
巴里  等等
Barry, hold up.
怎么了
Hey, what?
刚才的情形你也看见了
You saw what happened in there.
琳达并没准备好
Linda's not ready.
她准备得足够好了
She is. She's ready enough.
你为什么这么着急
Why are you pushing this?
你为什么这么想  我只想抓住他
What-- why do you think? I want to get him.
到底想抓住谁
Get who, exactly?
那算是个问题吗
Is that a real question?
你说呢
You tell me.
我不确定这真的是跟极速有关
I'm-- I'm not sure this is even about Zoom.
我开始认为
I'm starting to feel like
你始终在追逐逆闪
you're still chasing the Reverse Flash.
逆闪已经死了
Reverse Flash is dead.
是的  但他对你做了那些事后
Yeah, but after all he did to you,
你却不是最后阻止他的那个人
you weren't the one that stopped him.
我们一起努力才完成的
We all worked together.
是的  但最后是艾迪毁灭了他
Yeah, and Eddie got him in the end.
那会不会让你觉得被骗了
I mean, did that make you feel cheated,
就好像根本没有报仇一样
like you didn't get your revenge,
而阻止极速就是你现在所能做的最好的事
and stopping Zoom is the next best thing?
我想说的就是
Look, all I'm saying is,
如果你要让琳达那样的人冒上生命危险
if you're gonna ask people like Linda to risk their lives,
你最好确定他们为什么要这样做
you better be sure of exactly why they're doing it.
很抱歉  我是个差劲的超级反派
Look, I'm sorry I'm a terrible supervillain.
你来这只会让我感到更糟糕
I don't need you to come here and make me feel worse.
我并不是为此而来
That's not why I'm here.
无所谓  我做不到的
Doesn't matter, I- I can't do this.
我根本就不是她
I just don't have it in me.
不对
That's not true.
你是我见过的最勇敢的姑娘
You're one of the strongest women I've ever met.
你潜力无限
You can do anything.
你又是怎么如此了解我的呢
And you know that about me based on what exactly?
琳达
Linda,
你信任我
you are trusting me.
所以我也要信任你  完全信任
So I need to trust you fully.
我知道你可以做到
I know that you can do this...
是因为我了解你
because I know you.
巴里  苍天啊
Barry. Holy crap.
我竟然和闪电侠亲热过
I've made out with the Flash.
听着
Listen,
我只是想跟你和解
I just want to bury the hatchet
然后感谢你所做的一切
and say thank you for all your work.
不用客气
You're welcome.
好吧
Okay.
这个触发机关可能卡住了
I think maybe the trigger mechanisms are just sticking.
不是触发机关的问题
It's not the trigger mechanisms.
-加点油润滑一下  -不是这样的  别
- I think-- it's just a little bit of oil. - It's not the-- no
我会很快收拾干净的
I'm just gonna clean this up really quick.
别碰我
Do not touch me.
我只是想帮忙
I'm just trying to help.
我知道威尔斯去另一个地球了
I know Wells went to the other Earth.
他为什么去哪里
Why?
我不知道  我发誓
I don't know, I swear.
你的忠诚令人佩服
Your loyalty is admirable,
杰西
Jesse.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
中城警局
乔  光博士
Joe, Doctor Light.
-不是已经不提这事了吗  -不  并没有
- I thought we settled that. - No, we didn't.
她仍然逍遥法外
She's still out there on the loose--
她这个超能力者可是谋杀了一个人的啊
a meta-human who just murdered a man.
我们难道就不采取些行动吗
Why aren't we doing something about it?
这一切都说不通啊
Look, none of this makes any sense,
你还一个字都不跟我说
and you're not talking to me.
好  好  好  听着
All right, all right, all right, look.
事情有点复杂
It's a bit complicated,
但我们现在还不能追查光博士
but we're not going after Doctor Light right now.
你得信任我  帕蒂
I need you to trust me, Patty,
过几天我就告诉你
for a few days or so.
你与这事有牵连吗
Are you somehow involved in this?
你是问我有干违法的事吗  没有
If you're asking if I'm dirty, no,
但我需要时间来处理些事情
but I need some time to take care of some things.
我信任你  真的
I trust you, I do.
我要是不信任你  就不会做你的搭档
I wouldn't be your partner if I didn't.
是你不信任我
This is about you not trusting me.
-帕蒂  我信任你  -还不够
- Patty, I trust you. - Not enough.
几天后就真相大白了
A few days.
今晚想一起吃饭吗
Do you want to maybe grab dinner tonight?
有点事情  我想听听你的意见
I could use your opinion about something.
今晚不行  抱歉
I can't tonight. I'm sorry.
没事
Sure.
事实上乔和我今晚
I-I would. Joe and I actually--
今晚有点事要处理
Joe and I have a thing that we've gotta do tonight.
那改天吧
Some other time.
我很想今晚和你在一起
I would much rather be spending the evening with you.
真的  要是没这些事  我一定和你吃饭
Seriously, if I could cancel these plans, I would.
我们明天一起吃晚饭好吗
Can we do dinner tomorrow?
好  没问题
Yeah, I would like that.
好  那回见
All right, I'll see you.
祝你今晚一切顺利
Good luck with your thing.
谢谢  我想我需要你的理解
Thanks. I think I'll need it.
我是来杀闪电侠的  没人能阻止我
I'm here to kill the Flash, and no one can stop me!
这怎么样
How's that?
演得有点过了
It's a little too much.
别摆弄耳机了
Stop messing with the earpiece.
最好不要把耳机弄掉了
Yeah, you don't want to dislodge it.
好  你说过的  抱歉
Right, you-- you told me that. I'm sorry.
不用抱歉  你做得很好  琳达
No, no, you're doing great, Linda.
很好  光博士  我来了
All right, Doctor Light, here I am.
你说你要杀了我
But we're gonna skip the part
恐怕咱们得跳过这部分
where you say you're gonna kill me
直接进入你杀不了我这部分
and go right to the part where I don't let you.
我是来杀你的  闪电侠
I'm here to kill you, Flash.
等一下  你在干嘛
Wait, what are you doing?
那段跳过了吗
We're skipping that?
是的
Yes.
我对极速是忠诚的
I am loyal to Zoom,
准备好被烤熟吧
so get ready to fry.
下次我们再这么搞
Next time we're doing this,
我准备写个好点的对白
I'm writing better dialogue.
-还有下次  -还有下次
- Next time? - Next time?
击中你了
Gotcha.
-是的  中了  -很好
- Yeah, you did. - Real good.
好吧
All right.
放马过来吧
Bring it on.
我说过了
Told you,
极速总是赢家
Zoom always wins.
你没事  对吧
You're okay, right?
没事  我必须演得像一点
Yeah, yeah. I had to make it look good.
好了  极速  我按你说的做了
Here it is, Zoom, I did what you wanted.
把我带回家吧
Now bring me home.
快出来
Come on.
快出来  快出来
Come on. Come on.
这就是他想要的一切吧
This is everything he wants, right?
快出来  极速
Come on, Zoom.
别搞小动作了
Hey, stop fidgeting.
不好意思  已经过去一小时了
Sorry, it's been an hour.
我落地的姿势太别致
I landed in a ridiculous position,
我的脚感觉麻了
and my foot fell asleep.
他大概只是想看看你是不是真死了
He's probably just waiting to see if you're really dead.
他随时可能发起进攻
Any minute now, he's gonna strike.
不
No.
抱歉  可能是我搞砸了
Sorry, I probably screwed up somehow.
没有  琳达  你做得很好
No, Linda, you did great.
看来威尔斯是受够了
So Wells ain't taking this well.
你呢
How about you?
没错  这确实很糟糕
Yeah, it just sucks, you know.
有些事你说对了
You were right a little bit
这一切不只是极速的问题
about this not being just about Zoom--
还有逆闪电的问题
about it being about the Reverse Flash.
好吧
Okay.
但原因不是你想的那样
But not for the reason that you think,
不是因为我没打败他
not because I didn't beat him.
因为  威尔斯...
It's-- Wells--
在视频里承认谋杀我妈妈前
he said something to me on that video
他和我说了一些话
before he confessed to my mom's murder.
他说  即使他死了
He said that even if he was dead,
他还是胜利了  因为我并不快乐
that he still won because I wasn't happy,
而且我永远不会真正快乐
that I'd never really be happy.
他凭什么这样说
How the hell would he know?
他了解我  他了解未来的我
He knew me. He knows future me.
那是未来的你  这个你是在当下
That's future you. This is the you here and now.
我依然觉得威尔斯说得没错
I still think that Wells is right.
自从我穿越回那天晚上
Ever since I went back to that night
我却没能救下她  没救下我妈妈
and I didn't save her-- I didn't save my mom,
这在我心里一直是个空洞
I just-- there's just been this void in me.
知道吗  我觉得这个空洞会一直伴着我
You know, I just feel like that is always gonna be there.
不管是好是坏  威尔斯是了解我的
For better or worse, Wells-- he knew me.
比我还了解你吗
Better than I know you?
他也许跟踪了你15年  但是我养了你
He may have stalked you for 15 years, but I raised you.
威斯尔说那些话  是为了惹火你
Look, Wells said what he said to you to mess with you--
为了最后给你洗脑一次
to get in your head one last time.
如果你听信了他  他就得逞了
If you listen to him, you let him win.
我知道  我不想那样
I know. I don't want that.
你的快乐你自己主宰  巴里
You're responsible for your own happiness, Barry.
忘了威尔斯吧
Forget about Wells.
好好想想自己要什么  让自己快乐的是什么
Think hard about what you want and what makes you happy.
奋力去争取
Go out and get it.
就这么简单
Simple as that.
好吗
All right?
好的
Yeah.
看看他们的眼睛  太好玩了
And look at their eyes. Amazing.
很高兴见到你们
Oh, good to see you guys.
-再见  -再见  帕蒂
- Bye. - Bye, Patty.
你看这段
Have you seen this
婴儿过隧道时表情的视频了吗
video of babies' expressions as they go through tunnels?
他们的小脸太有爱了
Their faces are priceless.
我不是孩子迷或...
I'm not baby crazy or--
这个是某种奖励吗
What did I do to deserve that?
我一直在考虑什么能让我快乐
I've just been thinking about what makes me happy,
开始了解你让我很开心
and getting to know you makes me happy.
那我们应该多做做类似的事
We should do more of that then.
中城新闻图报
希望我至少能留着那双手套
I wish I could have kept the gloves at least.
你要拿来做什么
What would you have done with them?
戴去狂欢
Raves, duh.
你不是这么想的
That is not what you were thinking about.
我在想很多事
I was thinking about a lot of things.
比如所有发生在我身上的事
Like how everything that's happened to me
这几天的事是我绝对
the past few days is the best story
写不出来的
I can never write.
谁说不是呢
Ooh, tell me about it.
你会习惯吗
Do you ever get used to it?
保守这么大的秘密
Keeping a secret that big?
不习惯
No.
太沉重了
It's pretty heavy.
我要好好地睡一觉
I need a good night's sleep.
先走了
I'm gonna head out.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
如果我们要做闪电侠的同伴
Oh, hey, if we're gonna be The Flash's sidekicks,
也许我们应该一起去健身之类的
we should probably join CrossFit or something, you know?
-没错  -没错
- Oh, yeah, girl. - Yeah.
拜
Bye.
琳达
Linda!
好了
There you go.
你以为这些东西
It's like you think these things
会突然从树上长出来吗
just grow on trees or something.
上一个却被咱们白白地扔掉了
And we threw away the last one for nothing.
这监控录像你已经看几十次了
You've been going over this footage dozens of times.
每一件事完全照计划进行
Everything went exactly according to plan.
如果是  极速早就出现了
If it had, Zoom would have shown up.
也许光博士是错的
Maybe light was wrong.
也许他无法看穿缺口
Maybe he can't see through the breaches.
或许他最终决定放弃了
Or maybe he finally decided to give up.
爱瑞丝  慢点说  我不明白
Iris, slow down. I can't understand you.
极速抓了琳达
Zoom has Linda.
他在楼顶
He's on the roof.
放开她
Put her down.
你喜欢用鱼饵来钓鱼吗
You like to fish with bait?
我也喜欢
I do too.
你得赶紧离开这里
You need to get out of here, okay?
不  你打不过那东西的
No, you can't fight that thing.
它就是个怪物
It's a monster.
快走
Just go.
极速不可能是人类
Zoom cannot be human.
他是  或曾经是
He is...or was.
巴里要怎么打败它
How the hell is Barry supposed to defeat that?
他为什么跑掉了
Why is he running away?
他没跑掉  他不害怕
He's not. He's not scared.
他准备要对他使用雷霆一击
Ooh, he's gonna thunderbolt him!
什么
What?
杰伊教他如何抛掷闪电
Jay taught him how to throw lightning.
你们看到了吗
Did you guys see that?
看到他用恶魔利爪抓住了闪电吗
See him catch a bolt of lightning with his demonic claws?
看到了
Yeah, saw that.
杰伊说得对  他不能独自战斗
Jay was right. He cannot do this alone.
他不是独自战斗
He's not alone.
-快跑  巴里  -不
- Run, Barry. - No.
我要看看威尔斯速度抑制血清是否有用
I'm gonna see if Wells' speed-dampening serum works.
你想怎么样
What do you want from me?
想要一切
Everything.
你想要成为我  是吗
You want to be me? Is that it?
你想要做英雄吗
You want to be a hero?
英雄会死
Heroes die.
你得能追上他们
Only if you can catch them.
巴里的速度怎么敌得过极速的速度
How is Barry gonna match Zoom's speed?
真是天才  他不是在赛跑
Genius. He's not gonna match it.
他要把把自身速度剔除在外
He's gonna take it out of the equation altogether.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
终极速度
Terminal velocity.
物体坠落可实现最大速度
The highest velocity attainable by a falling object.
-空中坠落吗  -自由坠落一击
- Falling through the air? - Yeah, freefall fight.
他们的牵引阻力等同于向下的重力
Their drag force equals the downward force of gravity,
合力为零  变成...
making the net force zero, making--
相等的速度  太聪明了
Equal velocities. That is genius.
永远别忘了
Never forget,
我是现今世上速度最快的人
I am the fastest man alive.
他快被杀死了
He's killing him.
巴里
Barry.
接下来就该你了
You're next.
巴里
Barry.
看看你们的英雄
Look at your hero.
这个人不是神
This man is no God.
他什么都不是
He is nothing!
中城警局
有闪电侠保护这座城市的日子已经终结
The days of The Flash protecting this city are over.
-别开枪  -把他放下
- No, hold your fire. - Put him down.
如果你们没有了宝贝英雄又该怎么办呢
Now what will you do without your precious hero?
快开枪  现在
Shoot that thing, now.
想得美
Nice try.
-有消息吗  -没有
- Anything? - No.
-你找到他了吗  -没有
- Do you have him? - No.
巴里
Barry!
哈里森·威尔斯
Harrison Wells,
你以为用他你就能打败我了吗
you thought you could defeat me with this?
我犯了个错误
I made a mistake.
没错  一个代价高昂的错误
Yes, a costly one.
再见  闪电侠
Good-bye, Flash.
你一样也是不够快
You, too, weren't fast enough.
不  不
No. No!
保持清醒  保持清醒  巴里
Stay with me. Stay with me, Barry.
别离开我  求你  巴里  拜托
Stay with me. Please, Barry, please.
这都怪你  如果巴里死了  你也要陪葬
This is all you! If Barry dies, you die.
乔  巴里的生命体征已经稳定了
Joe, Barry's vitals have stabilized.
放开他吧
Let's let him go.
不  凯特琳
No, Caitlin.
为什么  这对巴里有什么好处
Why? What good does that do for Barry?
这对我有好处
It's gonna help me.
乔  住手  谁是杰西
Joe, stop. Who's Jesse?
你是怎么
How do--
杰西是我的女儿
Jesse's my daughter.
极速抓走了她  你真的用震波感应了我
Zoom has her. You've-- you did vibe me.
-是的  -你看到了什么
- Yes. - What did you see?
我看见了你女儿
I saw your daughter.
她和极速在一起
She was with Zoom.
她还活着吗
But she's alive?
是的
Yeah.
和其他人一样是极速把你送到这来的吗
Zoom sent you here like the others?
你杀了闪电侠  就可以找回你女儿吗
You kill The Flash, and you get your daughter back?
唯一找回我女儿的办法就是
The only way I get my daughter back is,
我抓住极速
I capture Zoom.
你明白吗  你爱巴里
Do you understand? You love Barry.
我爱我女儿
I love my daughter.
而且只要极速还活着
And none of these children are safe
没有人会是安全的
as long as Zoom is here.
我试着在我的地球上抓住他
I tried on my Earth to capture him.
但我失败了
I failed.
我以为我可以把他带来这里
I thought I could bring him down here
让巴里帮助我
with Barry's help.
我错了
I was wrong.
我觉得他快要醒了
I think he's waking up.
巴里  巴里
Barry. Barry?
能听见我说话吗
Can you hear me?
你真是吓死我们了
You scared the crap out of us.
你昏迷了很久
You were gone for a long time.
情况有多糟
How bad is it?
很糟
Bad.
如果不是你恢复这么快的话  我真的很担心
If you didn't heal so quickly, I'd be very worried.
-琳达  她还好吗  -她没事了
- Linda, how is she? - She's fine.
她去了海滨城和几个朋友待在一起
She's staying with some friends out in Coast City.
极速呢
Zoom?
还是等你能起身好转之后
Let's-- let's worry about Zoom
再来担心极速吧  好吗
when you're up and about, okay?
不行  你需要躺着
Oh, no, you're staying put.
没错  说真的  你这次伤得挺重的
Yeah, seriously, you got your ass kicked.
不  伙计们  我的腿没有知觉了
No, guys, I can't feel my legs.
我的腿没有知觉了
I can't feel my legs.